[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Journey to the Center of the Earth guide Hans Belke has what kind of pet?", "correct_answer": "Duck", "incorrect_answers": ["Squirrel", "Peacock", "Rooster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Dustin Hoffmans character in the 1967 movie The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "Benjamin Braddock", "incorrect_answers": ["Joseph Robinson", "Carl Smith", "Carter Robinson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does Jack hit Tyler in the first swing of their first fight in the film Fight Club?", "correct_answer": "The Ear", "incorrect_answers": ["The Stomach", "The Nose", "The Chin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many legs do ants have?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "8", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who coaches the ice-skating girl who switches sides at the end of For Your Eyes Only?", "correct_answer": "Jacoba Brink", "incorrect_answers": ["Solveig Marklund", "Georgette  Cousineau", "Ekaterina Pulyanin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Aristocats, Thomas and the cats finally reach the mansion where the cat family lives only to be caught again by the butler. Where does he hide them after he puts them into a sack?", "correct_answer": "In an oven", "incorrect_answers": ["In the loft", "In the stable", "Under his bed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nutrias belong to the rodent family.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1992 movie received the Oscar for Best Picture at the 65th Academy Awards in 1993?", "correct_answer": "Unforgiven", "incorrect_answers": ["A Few Good Men", "Scent of a Woman", "The Crying Game"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dr. Ross Geller from the TV show Friends teaches paleontology at this university in New York City.", "correct_answer": "New York University", "incorrect_answers": ["Rockefeller University", "Columbia University", "Fordham University"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1930s movie King Kong, the giant ape battles a pterodactyl.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the most popular color of bubble gum.  When gum had to be released on the market, it was the only color the inventor had on hand.", "correct_answer": "Pink", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue", "Green", "White"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A caries is formed as a result of food debris. Food remnants mix with saliva and bacteria, and result into this mixture that glues to the teeth.", "correct_answer": "Plaque", "incorrect_answers": ["Starch", "Dirt", "Amalgam"]}]